You stay here I'm going to telephone.
Chan Gee I'm mighty glad to see you again
challenged Captain Flynn must have
a way to make over Fred.
Fast as usual I'm in town on
a an hour already you have telephone
wire the minute I git telegram I started
watching all kinds. Contact mysterious
Mister I was sure it came up to me to get
out the train and I just saw my man alone
and I have trailed him seven now Rush No
you'll fall on him he couldn't help it I
think if you're about to make an important
arrest we've kept close to it
John that was over there. Did
not want to arrest him.
He'll keep getting rushes
agent pay or someone trying to steal
radar secrets from our government really
wanted you to locate him so I could observe
him myself so you could tell him to the
head of the gang was trying to steal the
raid and. I'm awfully sorry Charlie.
Don't matter no matter what apps
we arrest him and. Then we put him
someplace where you not
be shot it anymore.
She was this crime all know
all that is back and we got
a still on the boat all
right let's go.
On and then
you. Log on for our
route.
Instead just after that
the last twenty minutes
every so I'm going to
step in drive Day parade.
I'm afraid Captain. Arrive and the
party car on dock which justly
and I didn't even look at
the license plate I love
it because I don't act this is fun talking
we just brought in the homicide get
there quick I'm proud Well yeah
thanks just. Give me the radio.
Then talk it's that kind of stolen car
number ninety two X. Five four I'm a two X.
Five hole Yeah that's cause been
a part of stone by Miss Diane hall radioactive
something cause I'm already of sound
as well radio center they broadcast by
television Yeah their offices are on the
tenth fall and floor same floor
as Hamilton Research Laboratory
and say doesn't that for the
Hamilton experiment in great. Radio
they will soon make mistakes and fall.
Tonight if he and a black market man man
a Birmingham and I can prove it if
he's right that man's business is
a dark as you know exactly
that and you identify him from
a picture man as I am with that man I hate
to think of what I take up that makes me
blush here look so this is in
the fine and I hope it isn't
and the music no that's absolutely.
Welcome it could be him no wonder what do
you do is limited to the ghetto in this
film is then how if you make
them for the shoot and I. See
you been. You. Know that I
am it's wrong to get turned up there was
a quick thought at based on the suggested
character you don't want to see that the
movie will look over and I read your
piece battle you know I want to look at
a bar with all
the witches over said What do you know
about that will you see us and then God I
mean this is really
a he did this to me mastery I want the
ball you know when I win the contest when
you come you should see me
then I jumped up here's
a step idea to think you can do.
You expect us to believe that.
It could be argued to trying to get us I'm
going to run you're both in but women
can't do that's what I came here to while
you're you don't know who you know I had
Hey wait a minute let's find
out how these two as a child
a chance son so I'm sorry I must apologize
Captain parties say is true this is
number three son Tommy and this one
is second assistant Birmingham both
times often feeble minded. Now you do
a supposed to check very good still photo
with the POV that we came looking for you
you know we have to look after you you don't
go after me until I'm out of sight all
part of you know we're
a big help to you your worries all are we
in fact no trouble or too big for us some
of your trouble too big for me and we
must investigate Speicher's murder murder
Well here I come yeah go.
So you know the last she could
do that to me I've been
a momma most of my own she gave don't have
to meet Mr James Mr Chan come get me out
please I'm changing my mind.
Mr Brant the manager coming
right up must thank you I was
depressed so having to meet you I'm sorry
to keep you waiting but we just finished
a broadcast. Why do you wish to see
Miss will. Wish to speak to Mr Hall
regarding automobiles
Oh well right this way
I'm often often not so violent from the
flock to my nose doing all the angles we
have to learn to walk on the scene and
yet try fix it to stuff and you see if
you're off who are you want to run to and
I'm talking to him This is Birmingham
systems
a child of ten the world famous detective
holder with your uni started. This
way they told me to advertise
on the air what any
program that smells like the one you people
just put on Meet the air and you think
I'm going to continue
paying you. This is radio
I try to put on
a program and the monitor him self lets
the tourist Agapit us like goldfish which
is more about people who have
a point where you were supposed to definitely
inform the management that I was no
sightseers in the studio by my
actors were either rehearsing
a broadcast and wire nevermind making
excuses this is marsh these people are not
tourists. This gentleman is here because.
It's something I'm sure it won't happen
again you've said that they thought and so
if you don't talk back to me well pop do
you want any wish private conversation
with Mr Hall you wish to see me
you are Mr Hall Yes me to introduce myself
permit me to the past breaking into
conferences if I'm paying for all comforts
I have drawn a chance representative of
a federal government federal government
along oh well on the low rise Willie
Randolph hard to lose
it's hard to know if you would have parked
car stolen. But it wasn't stolen it was
merely borrowed by whom please well.
I don't know you see Gloria I
know excuse me this is Gloria Bay Mr Chairman
after rehearsal tonight Gloria and I
went out to the park and Diane was gone
so I telephoned police then we went to
a restaurant ate talked to some friends
came back up here and there was Diane's car
right back in the parking their car missing
about eight thirty tonight that's right
but how did you know and why should the
federal government be interested in
a stolen car that wasn't completely stolen
that is all the most fortunate to have
met such charming radio ladies hope
to meet you again very soon perhaps.
Beg your pardon. To meet a gentleman
apologizes for bumping you in the States is
a rare thing in his you that coward of
a gent I give you credit. Mr
Chen This is Mr Harz Callar
speech experience actor now of motion
pictures radio and television Mr best
interests once the full most Shakespearean
actor of my time but now all chars.
Now I am known only for the mass
behind which I hide when I paid
a man. On the radio screen and. Two it
is
a living and so good night
to you while and all. Carl
as act on all the did you learn everything
that you came to see was all about yes
thanks for all kinds of assistance good
if you will excuse that in the pop
idol kit we came all the way
from New York City following
a man named Rob Ross was murdered to the
same person who leaves here played on
a lot right shoe print is
duplicate of one on the
cabinets during the rush
murder. Someone who are
recently but up someone
we all see the most
interesting place visit to model.
Manager please call this is Brett
Rush was contacted he was scared
that the police were after him he was ready
to blab because Charlie Chan was effort
to be can talk now.
I borrowed the annus car
last night to go meet route.
Information I want the address of the
telephone number Harding two five three five
yes I know but this is back to Grady
praising station twenty seven
where Office two eleven
have gone belly Thank you.
Next August please that's flurry of
a radioactive small time until she gets
Mrs March's program she's going to get
what Nora. Firehall radioactive
elements face me up to me
a few months ago nothing definite except
the lives of. Thank you so very much
Captain for your excellent report on my
list of suspects. You mean to tell me that
you really think that one
of these people here is
a murderer not only think so but
firmly believe so but which months
well gone are to try and find out which one
is guilty first and that's easy pop the
murderer will be the one with the guilty
look number three son have excellent
parents question have always
been what it contains
where lemonade been cut is not a
gentleman's car yet but it's been
a long time I haven't seen you so long and
then there are the last time I saw you
was the video I move on now so I moved
over to welcome you live in that
neighborhood I don't know where I'm living
I want to pay any debt she does show it
is. A huge deal my body
voiced. I know you have
a lot of you got me wrong you got me wrong
I got married again I should. Say not to
use the subject you got
a you know I don't know. Why didn't
you in The Help but I got on
a boat and you didn't answer the what was
about when I developed the condo that
turnip will play Yeah yeah it starts right
now more on the back. What do you do and
when I will say console to
a compendium make your sleep show not what
you should obtain I did you know what
those are going to like to.
See if agree with each other.
I was always about that laser it is
well thank you. I'll rely on the
outcome of that. And you didn't
see the head of the human.
You know pop I've got an idea about this
case. Well I had an ideal but at the time
no actual record not start in
solitary confinement even higher
rates were going out to
watch studio records or no
you've broken your promise to me just when
the landlord has broken our lives and
gotten the bobbins broken learn to read
this all grandmama what are we to do when
these are all right to our children Oh yes
but the usual too many hard to choose so
face the future was just my children for
tomorrow was to be in those days you
didn't chose to be what does
the future hold in store
for Jane and her so lovable
family have you tried
a Marshall's mellow mix waffles covered
with just over two of them orders of melted
butter eggs that you two sets of rules of
but us with the corrections to speculate
who wrote that AMES Well I thought
it sounded nice you thought that's
a lie the whole program sounds
a stupid as you should cancel my contract
here and get my account some of the
network measures Mars if that's how you
feel about it why don't you will I don't I
was depressed that US changed the script
and the announcement then do it so is
talking about it and you learn how
to talk like a human instead of
a bloke grab chains announce
us to also I. Sorry to
interrupt the going to your sorry if you
want to speak to Miss Hall again you can
wait to have finished so Sunday must
speak to everyone present all of us what
fly regarding
a murder murder yesterday you said you
were investigating my stolen car question
who stated your car commit
murder but who was killed
a mystery route I never heard of them
thank goodness if you know what I like to
get on really old Sometimes
if I can get don't do me
tell me what's the matter I gotta learn
that I want to meet with the legs won't
cooperate with you want to lean for way
I just saw something going there is
a combination between Dracula and
I was zombie just straight out of
a green the graveyard but old but that
I got to see with glee and I know hold
waterspout wish that a.
Nothing so excuse me
a phantom I was seeing thing. You did you
yeah it's hanging right on the don't
hang it in that the left
do. We go or send for
our from.
Those that always connect. Charlotte
chan to see you again most happy to
see you Mr Hamilton this is number three
son Tommy oil and Birmingham Brown is boys
are second team assistant you receive
my telegram and follow instructions
immediately on my radar equipment has been
taken away by the government what about
record of experiments and copies of secret
patents the government has the originals
I have my own copies in the safe hundreds
of safe only secure so long as someone
outside watching safe.
You know since receiving
a wire I found evidence of several attempts
to break in here do you think I don't
know how special gods know know that I
am present contents of safe becomes
a trap and papers inside are only bait
with which to catch and they may write to
a lot of dads and yes
useful gadgets to write
a hero if you get on the work but today
allows I might fighters to hunt down to
destroy enemy airplanes without
even seeing them. This long spooky
really read our. Read what is
read not well read on is was
sort of. But I may have don't you know
anything much about read as you do.
And you ought to know I've read what
is. A temperature of climatic tunnel
you make whether internal Yes that is the
extremes of heat and cold to test the
reliability of radar and
television and also it's
a primary conditions the tunnel has two
compartments one for you to one for cold
that's like Works
flashing whenever there's
a foreign body in the tunnel no matter
what the weather in there now this is
a for those who you know
what is. Thank you.
Thank.
You Karen. When it rains
laboratories do not know I'm
into
a strange machine strike the child
also keep things are out of sight
but I am so by dialing back you gotta
get I have to go back you. Go buy
a gun come in.
Yes if you for a moment Mr
Brett Mr Brett why all of
a formality Gloria I'm here on business I
want better parts and more money starting
tomorrow you say that is if you were
ordering me to give them to you I Look here
young lady said I'm getting one part you're
liable to lose though you already have
I wouldn't be subject to Mr Beck you better
listen to please very I'm busy remember
these remember them but you mean that's
the last pack of my private matches
used and I gave them to you yesterday
morning and this is that entitle you to
order me to give you better jobs I am car
was stolen I found these later in the
seat
like me all that said isn't craft I
just better give these to Mr Chan and
see what he says oh wait and see that
you get better jobs thank you so
.
The manager please call this
is Brett talking this I'm
very a Bain an actress
here knows that you die on
a horse car last night she's
like maybe me but I do.
Personally I think the program needs
a tire change of personality however I
listen for my office and then I'll decide
what to say and don't say come on how can
we solve a case just by watching people to
a glass what Detective nay just great
patience Oh I know that when it comes to
detective work I'm on my p's and q's What
are you familiar with the rest up for
that oh well to drink when you want some
drove I'm just sorry not to go my broken
motor you drank it shares are
burned I will order for you out
a way to do. Troubles not seeing the troubles
there exists in the city we must move
by the first of
a month and with no place to go why
can't we settle down and be like
other people so keep your chin up
movies and look on the brighter side
of course grandma you're always right over
at the start of Meghan why
I would all benefit of
a good living by shows all about like well
a part of that that is not as bad as usual
you start to put it on the end and stop
getting about coming around you want to
stand here talking all night can I get you
anything wrong cigarettes
right. You give me
a light press where of course.
That are.
Glorious. And that young lady fresh you
know we're all right here in here.
They just pop yes please why is it the
Whenever anything happens around here you're
always on her desk just like they
always say down at the office
it's home I know the cigarette
show is just so but that isn't
a reason why you should slip
a cigarette butt from the lid you know I
don't smoke what other people try to grab
often turn out to be valuable to clue to
what will that's what will have to find no
you just include need how did anybody call
a doctor Dr No you know young
lady already dead dead
chrono was right or what he said misspelling
was punished tactic reaction proves
she was but I don't know what type always
but you never run into it before. You
suspect any of the people who are present
when she died I suspect everyone on
general principle but do assistance already
watching person who interests me most
Thank you so much Dr and I have
a night over
to you Brooke.
Not brought now but on
a breath
now instead of broad it was pretty when
we work in France together. Like we're
working together again but I recognize
your voice in my phone asking for the
manager please so you're the manager
and Man of the party. Not me
I get that on the phone someone else
someone unknown to me. If the caller is
OK call us which to wife must line see
how do you care if we don't know who our
boss is we've got that way before I've got
to know COOPER There's been two murders
on this job already two murders.
He won't tell me we should know the
name of the boys to protect us this.
Who's calling.
It works. I see. If you learn anything
that we know we don't need
a lot of information we
have to squeal. Some
of coming.
You'll hear nothing which is
said inside strange office just
a moment of the jungle mischance but outside
of all you ever hear Mr Kopper call Mr
Brecht Mr Brock That's right pop managing
to challenge British intelligence seeking
espionage agent named Ralph brought Ross
brought on the radio station manager calls
him temporary Brett nothing in office
except table chair and telephone
and yes it must have been
a reasonable good office because he
was just as clean as I is when I make
a bit Captain please detail
a man to check on people coming and
going from office to eleven. Right.
Really we make Mr Brett surprise visit
boy here we go again surprise visits no
surprise only
read absent downstairs also here
you think he's run away pop
up that you print you're looking for
a person where this you go around
and Gosh you mean murdered No ROSS.
Was Locked the breath that was.
Manageable. Read this
Charlie Chan knows all
about the rush murder he's after
me you gotta protect me when I do.
Right here in this bill.
Dorman I'm sayin Mr Brett
still here has not let.
Mr Right you see you Mr Brett late night
I saw needs driving outside of his own
office and if there are
a couple of ex-wives in there waiting to
collect alimony. Not funny when you see
this about twenty minutes ago pop that's
when we were in there. Moustached police
to guard all doors police because
Fred is a murderer Brett
a murderer kills. Nice people I'm working
for Birmingham we've got to find bread to
wash around it because he'd kill us yeah
it'll just be man enough to catch up with
it come on. Say it's eight hours since right
it's been seen you know he might have
to hide out somewhere because you have man
parts that every accept he can't get by
them they go take
a look on various floors good. God
and change them possibly for
a cleaning some color. You
know Birmingham everywhere we
go we bump into that woman don't be so
suspicious told every one of you be telling
me I did.
Did you see in the last ten
minutes no no but there was
a fellow Him Yes Oh he need to know the
fellow I'm looking for I didn't say but if
you like till I got time no but maybe if
you could I'm busy that night or so much
yes Lydia do you think. I was
getting that problem I got
a phone no but I could if you will my cards
on the cell phone yes when I see you I
think you have
a thing you call me. Do you know
that he can't be that and so
the laboratory door is open do you suppose
Bethany Well if he is living today and
I'm tired of talking with them gadgets
Well you know you should be in this room.
Nobody home let's go. Look
thanks been wrong perhaps the robbers
too many robbers murders Well this is
a regular cleaning in time but
let's get out of the car come
could have been
a little light around you.
Oh I'm surrounded. They
disappoint a good hiding place let's take
a look at this take on the
number of the Hornets.
You know one time when the pill is called
Out of the only house I just gave So I
think I was doing outside just east
walked into Cuba oh he stay with me oh
gosh talking to the like the old
going to
own
.
The we're going to
cure
a cure they want to I don't
think you will lose you this is
going to act I stop you I was glad
oh OK I was going to stop.
It looks like the place is going to
have an option in this case no C.V.
I seem like indicate someone in Tanakh
want
a little. Oh. I want to hear. That I
was curious.
What a little tell off. To get on
a Sunday night I should just do it
yes I did want to ask if I will.
Go off it was better than I
working for you I mean give.
Us. All you.
Like you know why they're. Saying
thank you. Q
Will
.
All will kettle black
a little. KARNER just finished
Charlie he said but what voice
he died of a fall from
a great high bred last seen alive
on second floor of cars mobility
later he found good content. Someone
would have us believe victim
eight stories up
oh look at the telephone I once
had for you didn't include. Yes
on we were Mr Cooper alias. Alias how
Charlie. I remember your sense of Lies
time I arrested you. Six years ago
in Singapore remember. I remember reading
a great pleasure to our rescue
again Mr Cooper our home you know
I'm not talking you talk with your friend
Mr Brett yesterday now he has murdered
credit card I had nothing to do with it I
don't know who I work for I'd only ask
someone else which is
a cough I know I have
a thing but
you find out in really installed rooms
to jam calls can be switched and you may
swear cos Which do you
know but it might take
a couple of days keep working gentleman
want to remain with Mr Cooper
he will continue to answer
a phone call you issue of how to do it
I'm not getting mixed up with murder.
Addiction the radio impersonator glad
to meet you Mr chat impression good
you know what you ought to do that that
Mr Brett not yet made public wish to try
experiments already so.
It's. Oh.
This is Brett calling hurry
it up right. I've got to see.
Dad.
What. Do the service elevator.
Come seventh law if I know what.
Tenth floor is known to lead to
Charlie wonder after to kill
a pop thank you so much the say nothing
of this to anyone I understand
no one since I pop we go ten floors.
Way. We've gotten from vice. You've gone
over that way we have killer between all
those logon. Runs out of
the. He knows along with
the. Fact.
That. Elevator
already arrived doesn't come
out of the he's going to miss
a chance for him to come get me out when
you've got to get down yourself get don't
own up without
a parachute drop into certain they're very
heavy What are you talking about Mr Jim
Well as you stand in the room floor before
I don't know whether that will come from
. What do you mean what floor come from
working in the channel when I was down on
the seven float that I'm
a beautiful one of them on the MIA let
me stand on up your imagine things for I
have known in the kitchen when I went in
that elevator they all available clothes
that pull one out from under me just like
a trap door and let me handle
mopping knew I was looking at
a time I would float straight down you mean
to say five or more of elevator follow
yesterday perhaps Mr
Brett received a message we've come to
the some floor down to the Thames pop in
a fate save us from dying shame why Mr
Brett. He was killed by far from very
high we did shame to
basement. Not elevated
blood stains on the floor of.
This is where Mr Pratt fall today
you're getting to be
a habit coming in here and interrupting
my program or so it's an outrage murder
also. Do you know what I pay for my problems
I'm interested only that murder show
pay for killing of myspace
and Mr Brett. You are
a person when myspace and I us do you think
these people would make or anyone that
too busy murdering the English language
testimony is misspending satiate more work
and more money or you did say something
like That's right who can give her more
work and more money there's direct Certainly
he's the slave driver rather he was
very friendly with Mr Burt's Jaya couldn't
stand him to be tested him and oh yes I
just remembered Gloria did say she talked
with prayer Gloria said he promised her
a lot more work I was surprised because I
knew he liked her know that and she liked
him
a great glow you did say something like
that something about about. Their shape
what Mr Ed Oh I don't
recall it's a guy gab
a lot not the people gab back at me I
can't remember half of the things I hear
please try to remember might be most
important to surely it will come back to me
and one that does I'll tell you right away
so thank you that is all thank you so
much thanks indeed companies that. Well
what do you make of
a challenge so many fish in fish
markets even Florida smell same
much confusion
week long twenty second this
is television next for metal
station W X K nine X.
Presenting Well here I am days comedian is
on conception of the Dance of the spirit
.
What you're doing here probably was
about to go out to look for you. On
a pop star that's an even number something
point what if you right after the show.
Oh Rachel.
A favor and then Nashville. And all of
these new gentlemen we
transfer you to tell
a studio Number two our Miguel Moreno
and his Marine Band carry on during the
second portion of the program. Well you
won't have your closing speech if you
forget it yes well what happened.
I don't know what distinguished.
This rent but three song Tommy Tommy you'll
remember something you wish to tell me
now I remember what Gloria
told me and I've got
a lot of good information for you too
Yes this afternoon when I was up on the
second floor I saw.
What's up on the. Alley it.
Gets cigarette smoke have same analyzed
quickly Mr Chester you'll come with me.
Mr Chen my office is never locked the
people on television ready or in and out of
here all hours
of Mr Chad I've never seen that thing
before my life my mama trees and I says
obviously controls which are
mysterious gardens service elevator Mr
Chester we visit Polish
headquarters. And was
poisoned by the same stuff that killed
in Spain but there was no poison in the
cigarette he smoked them is painful to
think about just before she died Poppy has
also given her by Mr Chester said Genesis
Keep it does not like women think felt I
took it away from her this is cigarette
smoke by Miss Baines this tested by you not
mention this before. I'll.
Smoke pours elicit
a release Mr Chester Oh but Charlie the
guy just did what the elevators in his
office surely must be the unknown if not
needed were after the pop question those
send messages to Mr Brett on Teletype
machine must have similar machine other end
of line there is no teletype instrument
and Mr Chester's office released him.
Trouble. From. Hi This program is
strictly slash it is transcription of
Life program made by misspelling when she
dies strangely only wish to hear and the
program we must move by the first of the
month and we have no place to
go why can't we pay you much
a step nearer the microphone turned
up by Him Now listen very quietly.
And feel like you hear strange noises Yes
popping when she was sobbing we same Nani's
on record Mr Rand's voice made during
television broadcasts the leave now know
how both Mr Bayne and Mr and work of
will need assistance of radio
technician to prove the right way.
It's
a flat Our Jonathan used in
making cups we have all named
Park proof now we've visited
studios see downstairs.
Margaret ready to do more business this
what we look for thank you so much
my radio man has
a stage still the all microphones are
examples of the shock wave radio beams sent
from some part of the building
explode those capsule
there is some sort of colorless gas in
the capsule to Cham the surface for the.
Cigarette please doctor did you stop
smoking pot. Would you kindly light saying
please.
Blow some smoke into the big. What is
a puff Well
that's it missed
a chance alone either the gas or the
cigarette is harmless but if someone first
inhale Guyse and then pretty soon smoke
cigarettes the combination of gas and
nicotine becomes
a poison and killed instantly thank you so
much Dr that is exactly what I wanted to
know. Every X.
Thought is not going to any of our people
leave the building this is Mr and Mrs
already here well just
a Nelson and Collins are in the building
even that wacky dentist cut off suspects
on the
T.V.
They don't know of any way agents. Have
office somewhere on this from our office
containing teletype machines
OK We have some find out
where they have taken so
long not me I like to
look hot tap and follow one.
Suppose this is the
machine we want but the.
Way radio used to explode.
On one of the stands one God you're next.
I go there and. We catch up with.
All.
The elevators you must have gone down.
He tried to come down the stairs when
I fired and he came back this way.
Again with just the elevator to someone
in the office so mostly the boy was open.
Trouble without costume disguise.
We find murder in
basement. Then you're not
a Swedish janitor is that all this is.
Government investigation I came here
a month ago. To keep on coming and
going from radar laboratory no one
suspected the genesis of being
a government operative. Very great. This
is my hello I never believed a
pop What about the photo of
a doll papers if she still I was this real
radar secrets remote some time ago if my
suggestion that's about it was her own
child and as usual end up case I have
discovered everything except where abouts
of my second assistant Birmingham bro you
know what did he call
it was play and all I want to do in the
face of this can be all right off this with
a pat pat coming after. All that's
me but let me see this thing
I think I'd rather take this.
God.